<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Hotel 1 -->
    <string name="hotelOneName">Hotel Monaco</string>
    <string name="hotelOneAddress">433 Chestnut Street, Old City</string>
    <string name="hotelOneDescription">With pet-friendly accommodations, new “Rocky” robes and a yoga mat upon arrival,
        this Kimpton Hotel property caters to Gen Y. The same holds true upstairs, where the Stratus Rooftop Lounge teems
        with an attractive crowd of young professionals.</string>

    <!-- Hotel 2 -->
    <string name="hotelTwoName">AKA Rittenhouse</string>
    <string name="hotelTwoAddress">135 South 18th Street, Rittenhouse</string>
    <string name="hotelTwoDescription">You probably already know about A.Kitchen and A.Bar, both see-and-be-seen spots with stellar menus.
        But you might not be as familiar with their namesake hotel, which is staffed with discreet, in-the-know concierges that can get you
        anything you might need on a moment’s notice</string>

    <!-- Hotel 3 -->
    <string name="hotelThreeName">The Logan</string>
    <string name="hotelThreeAddress">1 Logan Square, Logan Square</string>
    <string name="hotelThreeDescription">Housed inside the Four Season’s former digs, the Logan is the newest darling of Philadelphia’s
        hospitality scene. Forgoing blindingly bright furnishings for a subdued palette of grey and blue, guest rooms are sultry and sophisticated.
        Thanks to its recent December debut, the hotel — for now — remains relatively under-the-radar, ensuring individualized attention. Come spring,
        check out the highly anticipated Assembly Rooftop Bar</string>

    <!-- Hotel 4 -->
    <string name="hotelFourName">Hotel Palomar</string>
    <string name="hotelFourAddress">117 South 17th Street, Rittenhouse</string>
    <string name="hotelFourDescription">The in-room spa services at this sleek hotel are eco-friendly, organic, and best when scheduled à deux. Try the
        aromatherapy massage, which treats headache tension and stress, or the spirulina body wrap, which leaves skin taut and radiant. In the morning,
        draw a bath in the en-suite two-seater Fuji soak tub to maximize your Zen time</string>

    <!-- Hotel 5 -->
    <string name="hotelFiveName">Le Méridien</string>
    <string name="hotelFiveAddress">1421 Arch Street, Penn Center</string>
    <string name="hotelFiveDescription">Don’t let the fashionable bubble chandeliers fool you: This French-inspired hotel is committed to the classics.
        Its lobby bar — one of the chicest in town — is the ideal place for pre-dinner pommes frites and a glass of bubbly. Or, share a plate at Amuse,
        its on-site brasserie, which features French fare like escargot and frisée aux lardons. Book a light-filled suite for an impeccable view of the
        city.</string>
</resources>
