<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Philadelphia Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Tab Names -->
    <string name="tabOne">Hotel</string>
    <string name="tabTwo">Eat</string>
    <string name="tabThree">Shopping</string>
    <string name="tabFour">Play</string>

    <!-- Hotel 1 -->
    <string name="hotelOneName">Hotel Monaco</string>
    <string name="hotelOneAddress">433 Chestnut Street, Old City</string>
    <string name="hotelOneDescription">With pet-friendly accommodations, new “Rocky” robes and a yoga mat upon arrival,
        this Kimpton Hotel property caters to Gen Y. The same holds true upstairs, where the Stratus Rooftop Lounge teems
        with an attractive crowd of young professionals.</string>

    <!-- Hotel 2 -->
    <string name="hotelTwoName">AKA Rittenhouse</string>
    <string name="hotelTwoAddress">135 South 18th Street, Rittenhouse</string>
    <string name="hotelTwoDescription">You probably already know about A.Kitchen and A.Bar, both see-and-be-seen spots with stellar menus.
        But you might not be as familiar with their namesake hotel, which is staffed with discreet, in-the-know concierges that can get you
        anything you might need on a moment’s notice</string>

    <!-- Hotel 3 -->
    <string name="hotelThreeName">The Logan</string>
    <string name="hotelThreeAddress">1 Logan Square, Logan Square</string>
    <string name="hotelThreeDescription">Housed inside the Four Season’s former digs, the Logan is the newest darling of Philadelphia’s
        hospitality scene. Forgoing blindingly bright furnishings for a subdued palette of grey and blue, guest rooms are sultry and sophisticated.
        Thanks to its recent December debut, the hotel — for now — remains relatively under-the-radar, ensuring individualized attention. Come spring,
        check out the highly anticipated Assembly Rooftop Bar</string>

    <!-- Hotel 4 -->
    <string name="hotelFourName">Hotel Palomar</string>
    <string name="hotelFourAddress">117 South 17th Street, Rittenhouse</string>
    <string name="hotelFourDescription">The in-room spa services at this sleek hotel are eco-friendly, organic, and best when scheduled à deux. Try the
        aromatherapy massage, which treats headache tension and stress, or the spirulina body wrap, which leaves skin taut and radiant. In the morning,
        draw a bath in the en-suite two-seater Fuji soak tub to maximize your Zen time</string>

    <!-- Hotel 5 -->
    <string name="hotelFiveName">Le Méridien</string>
    <string name="hotelFiveAddress">1421 Arch Street, Penn Center</string>
    <string name="hotelFiveDescription">Don’t let the fashionable bubble chandeliers fool you: This French-inspired hotel is committed to the classics.
        Its lobby bar — one of the chicest in town — is the ideal place for pre-dinner pommes frites and a glass of bubbly. Or, share a plate at Amuse,
        its on-site brasserie, which features French fare like escargot and frisée aux lardons. Book a light-filled suite for an impeccable view of the
        city.</string>

    <!-- Play 1 -->
    <string name="playOneName">Reading Terminal Market</string>
    <string name="playOneAddress">1831 Chestnut Street</string>
    <string name="playOneDescription">The number one most visited attraction in
        Philadelphia is Reading Terminal Market, the city’s famous indoor food paradise
        that’s a one-stop shop for everything from local produce and delicious sandwiches
        to artisanal cheeses and desserts. Close to seven million people(!) visited the
        market last year and for good reason – it’s amazing. Check out our guide on 10
        great things to eat at the market before you go.</string>

    <!-- Play 2 -->
    <string name="playTwoName">Independence National Historical Park</string>
    <string name="playTwoAddress">1831 Chestnut Street</string>
    <string name="playTwoDescription">Known as the birthplace of American democracy,
        Historical Park (INHP) is located on the site of many of the seminal events
        that carried the nation through its founding as a global leader of democratic ideals.
        INHP welcomed more than 5 million visitors(!) in 2016. Will you be one of the millions
        to visit this year?</string>

    <!-- Play 3 -->
    <string name="playThreeName">SugarHouse Casino Philadelphia</string>
    <string name="playThreeAddress">1001 N. Delaware Avenue</string>
    <string name="playThreeDescription">SugarHouse Casino features 1,891 slots, more than 100
        table games and a 28-table poker room. The seven restaurants and bars, a multi-purpose
        event space and a seven-story parking garage help make the attraction one of Philadelphia’s
        premier entertainment destinations, attracting 3.6 million visitors in 2016.</string>

    <!-- Play 4 -->
    <string name="playFourName">Valley Forge National Historical Park</string>
    <string name="playFourAddress">1400 N. Outer Line Drive, King of Prussia</string>
    <string name="playFourDescription">No battles were fought in Valley Forge, but the time the
        Continental Army spent here went down as one of their most trying periods. Exhibits and
        artifacts in the Visitor Center, replicated huts and the original headquarters tell the
        story of the pivotal winter that George Washington and his troops endured. The 3,500-acre
        Valley Forge National Historical Park also includes trails and picnic areas and draws
        nearly 2.5 million visitors each year.</string>

    <!-- Play 5 -->
    <string name="playFiveName">The Liberty Bell Center</string>
    <string name="playFiveAddress">6th and Market Street</string>
    <string name="playFiveDescription">Many of the visitors to Independence National Historical Park
        (mentioned above) line up to see the Liberty Bell, one the park’s most most famous attractions
        that drew more than 2.3 million people last year. See the famously fractured bronze bell and
        snag a nice view of Independence Hall through the glass windows that look out over the park.</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 1 -->
    <string name="restOneName">The Parc</string>
    <string name="restOneAddress">Parc, 227 S. 18th Street</string>
    <string name="restOneDescription">Diners may feel as though they’ve gone transatlantic while hanging out at Parc,
        a Parisian-inspired bistro from prolific and James Beard Award-winning restaurateur Stephen Starr. Perched at
        tables across from Rittenhouse Square, diners can take in views of the park’s ever-present foot traffic while
        supping on the restaurant’s crusty fresh breads, onion soup and mussels simmered in dijon broth</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 2 -->
    <string name="restTwoName">The Love</string>
    <string name="restTwoAddress">130 S. 18th Street</string>
    <string name="restTwoDescription">Restaurateurs Aimee Olexy and Stephen Starr team up again — much to their fans’
        delight — for this bi-level restaurant and bar. The American menu features fresh, seasonal food, as well as the
        most important ingredient: the love</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 3 -->
    <string name="restThreeName">The Dandelion</string>
    <string name="restThreeAddress">124S. 18th Street</string>
    <string name="restThreeDescription">Modeled after the contemporary gastropubs in Britain, The Dandelion is a cozy eatery
        that invites Anglophiles to imbibe cask-stored pints and dine on delicious Welsh rarebit, an English cheddar-adorned
        burger or sticky toffee pudding. And, since a British-inspired restaurant would not be complete without afternoon tea,
        pots of tea with traditional fixings are available daily</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 4 -->
    <string name="restFourName">White Dog Cafe</string>
    <string name="restFourAddress">3420 Samson Stree</string>
    <string name="restFourDescription">More than 30 years ago, the White Dog Cafe started a trend in Philadelphia: an unusual
        blend of award-winning cuisine and social activism, including its focus on local, sustainable, organic ingredients.
        The whimsical dining rooms tucked inside three renovated brownstones make for an inspiring dining experience.</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 5 -->
    <string name="restFiveName">Bud and Marilyn's</string>
    <string name="restFiveAddress">1234 Locust Stree</string>
    <string name="restFiveDescription">This retro-inspired restaurant-bar from the same duo of Barbuzzo is named for Chef Marcie
        Turney’s restaurateur grandparents. The eatery serves new takes on American classics such as meatloaf, the wedge salad and
        chop suey, paired with cocktails like Marilyn’s O-F, a brandy Old Fashioned</string>

    <!-- Shopping 1 -->
    <string name="shoppingOneName">Rittenhouse Row</string>
    <string name="shoppingOneAddress">1831 Chestnut Street</string>
    <string name="shoppingOneDescription">Between the swanky high-rises, charming brownstones and Rittenhouse Square (one of Philly’s most popular parks),
        shoppers can find a reliable smattering of national and international retailers. Known as Rittenhouse Row, the area is one of the best places in
        Philly to wander around outdoors while stopping to pop in one store after the next.</string>

    <!-- Shopping 2 -->
    <string name="shoppingTwoName">13th Street in Midtown Village</string>
    <string name="shoppingTwoAddress">13th and Locust Street</string>
    <string name="shoppingTwoDescription">The stretch of 13th Street from Locust to Chestnut streets in Midtown Village is home to some of the city’s best
        restaurants, nightspots and gift shops — many of which stay open late to accommodate last-minute purchases or post-dinner treats.</string>

    <!-- Shopping 3 -->
    <string name="shoppingThreeName">Jewelers Row</string>
    <string name="shoppingThreeAddress">S. 7th and Sansom street</string>
    <string name="shoppingThreeDescription">Just steps from The Liberty Bell Center and Independence Hall is the country’s oldest diamond district,
        Jewelers’ Row. Dozens of vendors populate the blocks around 7th and Sansom streets, which has created a longstanding, gold-standard go-to for
        happy couples in search of a ring.</string>

    <!-- Shopping 4 -->
    <string name="shoppingFourName">University City</string>
    <string name="shoppingFourAddress">3500 Market Street</string>
    <string name="shoppingFourDescription">Catering to the college crowd that fills the area, University City houses trendy stores like Urban Outfitters,
        American Apparel and The Gap. You’ll also find bicycle shops, running shoe stores, bookshops and more, making shopping more convenient than ever.</string>

    <!-- Shopping 5 -->
    <string name="shoppingFiveName">Northern Liberties</string>
    <string name="shoppingFiveAddress">400 Spring Garden Street</string>
    <string name="shoppingFiveDescription">Just north of Old City, the burgeoning Northern Liberties neighborhood mixes art pioneers with modern apartment-dwelling
        professionals. Here, find everything from vintage retailers to handcrafted jewelry outlets to independent boutiques, scattered between the taprooms, BYOBs
        and cafes that fill the area.</string>

</resources>
