<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Shopping 1 -->
    <string name="shoppingOneName">Rittenhouse Row</string>
    <string name="shoppingOneAddress">1831 Chestnut Street</string>
    <string name="shoppingOneDescription">Between the swanky high-rises, charming brownstones and Rittenhouse Square (one of Philly’s most popular parks),
        shoppers can find a reliable smattering of national and international retailers. Known as Rittenhouse Row, the area is one of the best places in
        Philly to wander around outdoors while stopping to pop in one store after the next.</string>

    <!-- Shopping 2 -->
    <string name="shoppingTwoName">13th Street in Midtown Village</string>
    <string name="shoppingTwoAddress">13th and Locust Street</string>
    <string name="shoppingTwoDescription">The stretch of 13th Street from Locust to Chestnut streets in Midtown Village is home to some of the city’s best
        restaurants, nightspots and gift shops — many of which stay open late to accommodate last-minute purchases or post-dinner treats.</string>

    <!-- Shopping 3 -->
    <string name="shoppingThreeName">Jewelers Row</string>
    <string name="shoppingThreeAddress">S. 7th and Sansom street</string>
    <string name="shoppingThreeDescription">Just steps from The Liberty Bell Center and Independence Hall is the country’s oldest diamond district,
        Jewelers’ Row. Dozens of vendors populate the blocks around 7th and Sansom streets, which has created a longstanding, gold-standard go-to for
        happy couples in search of a ring.</string>

    <!-- Shopping 4 -->
    <string name="shoppingFourName">University City</string>
    <string name="shoppingFourAddress">3500 Market Street</string>
    <string name="shoppingFourDescription">Catering to the college crowd that fills the area, University City houses trendy stores like Urban Outfitters,
        American Apparel and The Gap. You’ll also find bicycle shops, running shoe stores, bookshops and more, making shopping more convenient than ever.</string>

    <!-- Shopping 5 -->
    <string name="shoppingFiveName">Northern Liberties</string>
    <string name="shoppingFiveAddress">400 Spring Garden Street</string>
    <string name="shoppingFiveDescription">Just north of Old City, the burgeoning Northern Liberties neighborhood mixes art pioneers with modern apartment-dwelling
        professionals. Here, find everything from vintage retailers to handcrafted jewelry outlets to independent boutiques, scattered between the taprooms, BYOBs
        and cafes that fill the area.</string>
</resources>