<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Restaurant 1 -->
    <string name="restOneName">The Parc</string>
    <string name="restOneAddress">Parc, 227 S. 18th Street</string>
    <string name="restOneDescription">Diners may feel as though they’ve gone transatlantic while hanging out at Parc,
        a Parisian-inspired bistro from prolific and James Beard Award-winning restaurateur Stephen Starr. Perched at
        tables across from Rittenhouse Square, diners can take in views of the park’s ever-present foot traffic while
        supping on the restaurant’s crusty fresh breads, onion soup and mussels simmered in dijon broth</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 2 -->
    <string name="restTwoName">The Love</string>
    <string name="restTwoAddress">130 S. 18th Street</string>
    <string name="restTwoDescription">Restaurateurs Aimee Olexy and Stephen Starr team up again — much to their fans’
        delight — for this bi-level restaurant and bar. The American menu features fresh, seasonal food, as well as the
        most important ingredient: the love</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 3 -->
    <string name="restThreeName">The Dandelion</string>
    <string name="restThreeAddress">124S. 18th Street</string>
    <string name="restThreeDescription">Modeled after the contemporary gastropubs in Britain, The Dandelion is a cozy eatery
        that invites Anglophiles to imbibe cask-stored pints and dine on delicious Welsh rarebit, an English cheddar-adorned
        burger or sticky toffee pudding. And, since a British-inspired restaurant would not be complete without afternoon tea,
        pots of tea with traditional fixings are available daily</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 4 -->
    <string name="restFourName">White Dog Cafe</string>
    <string name="restFourAddress">3420 Samson Stree</string>
    <string name="restFourDescription">More than 30 years ago, the White Dog Cafe started a trend in Philadelphia: an unusual
        blend of award-winning cuisine and social activism, including its focus on local, sustainable, organic ingredients.
        The whimsical dining rooms tucked inside three renovated brownstones make for an inspiring dining experience.</string>

    <!-- Restaurant 5 -->
    <string name="restFiveName">Bud and Marilyn's</string>
    <string name="restFiveAddress">1234 Locust Stree</string>
    <string name="restFiveDescription">This retro-inspired restaurant-bar from the same duo of Barbuzzo is named for Chef Marcie
        Turney’s restaurateur grandparents. The eatery serves new takes on American classics such as meatloaf, the wedge salad and
        chop suey, paired with cocktails like Marilyn’s O-F, a brandy Old Fashioned</string>
</resources>